[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120515pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 37, "question": "Because the question still remains who started the altercation?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "WP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 38, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120515pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 39, "question": "Isn't that the key question?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 40, "answer": "It's absolutely the key.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120515pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ":", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 47, "question": "When do we think he treated him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 48, "answer": "It was -- this record is from the next morning.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120515pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 70, "question": "Is that likely, do we think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 71, "answer": "We do think that's likely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120515pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 87, "question": "Is it likely they're going to chuck a hail Mary pass?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 88, "answer": "There's no way.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mary"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120515pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 98, "question": "Gloria, if you are prosecuting this, given everything you've seen to date, would you be pretty confident of a conviction now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", ",", "VBN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "NN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 99, "answer": "Well, I would always appear confident whether or not I was confident.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Cate Edwards"]}, "docId": "120515pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 118, "question": "Yes, Dan?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 119, "answer": "Kind of a no lose situation for the defense to be able to call Cate Edwards.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dan"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Gloria"]}, "docId": "120515pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 122, "question": "Because it is a kind of complicated question as to, will they be able to demonstrate what was in Edwards' head when most of the facts are not in dispute?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "TO", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "WP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "WRB", "JJS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 123, "answer": "I mean, Gloria, the stakes are very high here.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Edwards"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120515pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["MD", "RB", "VB", "JJR", "NNS", "IN", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBD", "VBN", "WDT", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 128, "question": "This couldn't be a higher stakes for John Edwards, could it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJR", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNPS", ",", "MD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 129, "answer": "Couldn't be higher stakes unless of course the death penalty were involved which of course it's not involved in this case.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["John Edwards"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120515pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 137, "question": "Dan?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 138, "answer": "Bottom line, this is a really unusual use of the law.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120515pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 145, "question": "Because once you start saying that private donations can be considered campaign contributions, even if they didn't go through the John Edwards for President fund, where does the line get drawn?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "NN", "NNS", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "NN", ",", "WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 146, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["John Edwards"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120515pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 153, "question": "Do they get swayed heavily by a man's demeanor?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "POS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 154, "answer": "I think absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120515pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 192, "question": "Can you imagine that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 193, "answer": "I don't want to, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120515pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 217, "question": "Ring familiar?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 218, "answer": "It's my style, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120515pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 231, "question": "Is that a compliment?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 232, "answer": "It is a compliment, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120515pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 242, "question": "What do you think of what's going on with this whole issue right now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "WP", "POS", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 243, "answer": "Well, this is the first time I've taken it personally.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Laura"]}, "docId": "120515pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NNP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 246, "question": "Where were you when you knew he'd done it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 247, "answer": "I was in the car and Laura, my wife, texted me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120515pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 253, "question": "Emotional?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 254, "answer": "Yes, it was very emotional.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120515pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 268, "question": "But what do you say to the people who aren't bigots but who have simply been brought up to believe in a religious matter this is fundamentally not what the bible says is right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "RB", "NNS", "CC", "WP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "VBN", "RP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "WP", "DT", "JJ", "VBZ", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 269, "answer": "Well, I don't -- I personally don't look to the bible as an authority document.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120515pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "NNP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 278, "question": "How much of bigotry -- how much of bigotry is basically ignorance, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "IN", "NN", ":", "WRB", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 279, "answer": "YNCH: Well, there's a lot of smart people who are bigoted.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120515pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 306, "question": "Like you were sick?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 307, "answer": "Yes, like I was sick.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120515pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 316, "question": "-- you were in your early 20s?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 317, "answer": "Thirties.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120515pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "CD", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 318, "question": "Your 30s?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 319, "answer": "I was in my 32 when I sent my parents a letter.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120515pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 320, "question": "So you've waited a long time?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 321, "answer": "I waited a long time, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120515pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 322, "question": "Did they know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 323, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120515pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 338, "question": "You now have both?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 339, "answer": "I have both, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120515pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 375, "question": "Haven't you seen \"Man Med\"?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "PRP", "VBN", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "."], "aSentId": 376, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120515pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 396, "question": "So you laugh at the role?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 397, "answer": "I do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120515pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 414, "question": "But it's just a great movie, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 415, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120515pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 422, "question": "How -- do you think, looking back, how lucky were you that fame came to you quite late?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "VBG", "RB", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "VBD", "TO", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 423, "answer": "Late, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120515pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "JJ", "IN", "CD", "CC", "CD", ",", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "CD", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 440, "question": "Well, what do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 441, "answer": "If I had gotten famous at 21 or 31, even -- I guess I was starting to get famous at 41 -- I would have been blown by this winds of public opinion.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120515pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "RB", "IN", "NN", ":", "DT", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 445, "question": "Do you not read any of that stuff?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 446, "answer": "Every once in awhile -- every once in a while I'll look at it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120515pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 450, "question": "You have been sober how long now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RBR", "WRB", "JJ", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 451, "answer": "Twenty years.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120515pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 452, "question": "Do you ever miss it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 453, "answer": "Not at all.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120515pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 454, "question": "-- partying, drinking?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "VBG", ",", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 455, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120515pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 473, "question": "Is it a constant battle?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 474, "answer": "No, not at all.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120515pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 500, "question": "Does all this make up for the loss of anonymity?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "DT", "NN", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 501, "answer": "You know, I'm still pretty anonymous.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120515pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 510, "question": "What is your view of the way the battle has been fought so far?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 511, "answer": "It's just such a shame we have this super PAC thing, I could almost cry.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120515pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 515, "question": "Does he have to?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "."], "aSentId": 516, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120515pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "VBN", ",", "CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 563, "question": "CNN, prime time talking about your life, given where you've come from?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 564, "answer": "I think the overwhelming part of it all has kind of lessened, but yes it does just feel like my God, when it is going to ever stop.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120515pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "NNP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 586, "question": "Why?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 587, "answer": "I would like to say I didn't have God in my life.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120515pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 596, "question": "When did it start going wrong for you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 597, "answer": "Well, I had taken on another relationship with someone else.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120515pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJR", "CC", "JJR", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 603, "question": "That created just a sort of -- an unbearable pressure, if you like?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBN", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", ":", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 604, "answer": "More or less, yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["1988"]}, "docId": "120515pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "CD", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 611, "question": "What was the first time for you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 612, "answer": "In 1988, as a congratulatory offer, some friends of mine congratulated me for having my first son.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120515pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "CD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "CD", "WDT", "VBZ", "RP", "DT", "JJS", "VBD", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "RB", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 645, "question": "ORGAN: When you look back on that, was that the lowest points, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "DT", ",", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJS", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 646, "answer": "It's one of the low points, but I guess the one that sticks out the most was when I was getting ready to feed my kids after three weeks of them not having a balanced home cooked meal.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120515pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", "NNS", ",", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 669, "question": "The people that you met on the streets, did you meet other people with similar stories to you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 670, "answer": "Oh yes, sure.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120515pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "NN", ",", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 671, "question": "Does it know any class, homelessness?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 672, "answer": "None whatsoever, none whatsoever.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120515pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", ",", "CD", "NNS", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 678, "question": "Many would argue -- you had how many children through this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "MD", "VB", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 679, "answer": "Nine, seven girls and two boys.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120515pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNS", ",", "NNS", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 682, "question": "Would you agree with that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 683, "answer": "At times, yes, sir.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120515pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 704, "question": "Did you have any idea when you did that little video for that guy how your life may possibly change?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP$", "NN", "MD", "RB", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 705, "answer": "None whatsoever.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["January 4th"]}, "docId": "120515pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "CD", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 712, "question": "When did you first realize it was beginning to take off?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 713, "answer": "Well, actually on January 4th of last year, I got a call.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120515pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "DT", ":", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "CC", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 722, "question": "What are the challenges still for you, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "RB", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 723, "answer": "I'm still -- the obsessions and all -- the obsessions and the desires, they come and go.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120515pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "VBG", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 734, "question": "To those who haven't had that stroke of luck, what is your message to them?", "question_pos_tagged": ["TO", "DT", "WP", "VBP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 735, "answer": "Keeping the faith that there is still a chance for a second chance, or maintaining hope and a desire to do better at some point.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]